
[
{"question": "ACP" ,
"answer": "Agile Certified Practitioner"
},
{"question": "Acceptance Test Driven Development" ,
"answer": "A method used to communicate with business customers, developers, and testers before coding begins."
},
{"question":  "Active Listening",
"answer":  "To focus on what is said and provide feedback to communicate understanding"
},
{"question":  "Adaptive Leadership",
"answer": "A leadership style that helps teams to thrive and overcome challenges throughout a project."
},
{"question":  "Affinity Estimation",
"answer":  "A method used to quickly place user stories into a comparable-sized group."
},
{"question":  "Agile" ,
"answer": "To develop a goal through periodic experimentation in order to fulfill the need of a complex decision."
},
{"question":  "Agile Adaption",
"answer":  "To adapt the project plan continuously through retrospectives in order to maximize value creation during the planning process."
},
{"question":  "Agile Coaching",
"answer":  "To help achieve goals that is either personal or organizational." 
},
{"question":  "Agile Experimentation",
"answer":  "To use the empirical process, observation, and spike introduction while executing a project to influence planning."
},
{"question":  "Agile Manifesto",
"answer": "A statement that reflects Agile Philosophy that includes: individuals and interactions over processes and tools, working software over comprehensive documentation, customer collaboration over contract negotiation, and responding to changes over following a plan."
},

{"question":  "Agile Manifesto Principles",
"answer":  "A document that describes the twelve principles of the Agile Manifesto."
}

]

